[
    {
        "question": "Which of these is a Python control flow statement type?",
        "choices": [
            "else if",
            "elif",
            "case"
        ],
        "answer": "elif"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these transports mail over the internet?",
        "choices": [
            "SMTP",
            "FTP",
            "HTTP"
        ],
        "answer": "SMTP"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is a valid HTML tag?",
        "choices": [
            "<body>",
            "<scroll>",
            "<website>"
        ],
        "answer": "<body>"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Python, which of these represents a decimal?",
        "choices": [
            "int",
            "float",
            "dec"
        ],
        "answer": "float"
    },
    {
        "question": "CSS stands for ____ Style Sheets",
        "choices": [
            "Cascading",
            "Cascaded",
            "Critical"
        ],
        "answer": "Cascading"
    },
    {
        "question": "Guido van Rossum created which language?",
        "choices": [
            "Python",
            "Perl",
            "COBOL"
        ],
        "answer": "Python"
    },
    {
        "question": "In C, what statement 'requires' another C file?",
        "choices": [
            "#include",
            "#require",
            "#import"
        ],
        "answer": "#include"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Lua, how do you get the length of a string?",
        "choices": [
            "string.len",
            "string.sizeof",
            "string.length"
        ],
        "answer": "string.len"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who maintains the HTML markup language?",
        "choices": [
            "WHATWG",
            "W3C",
            "Google"
        ],
        "answer": "WHATWG"
    },
    {
        "question": "In JS, how do you make something optional?",
        "choices": [
            "object?.key",
            "object.?key",
            "object[key]"
        ],
        "answer": "object?.key"
    },
    {
        "question": "In JS, what is Infinity-Infinity?",
        "choices": [
            "0",
            "NaN",
            "-Infinity"
        ],
        "answer": "NaN"
    },
    {
        "question": "```js\nlet x = parseInt('abc');```\nWhich of the following is true?",
        "choices": [
            "x === NaN",
            "x !== NaN",
            "x !== x"
        ],
        "answer": "x !== x"
    }
]